Guide to the Christmas Cards Reference Collection, 1940s-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Christmas Cards Reference collection 1940s-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.5 Linear Feet approx. 100 Items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Christmas Cards Reference Collection was compiled by the University Archives from a variety of sources for use in reference and research.
Collection Overview
The collection contains Christmas cards sent by various University units, including the Presidents Office, the Primate Center, the Stores, and many others. Many cards depict scenes of the campus. The collection has been used by various offices for inspiration in the design of cards.
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - Aging and Human Development, Duke Center for the Study of, undated (Box 1)
  - Alumni Affairs and Development, 1990s
  - Audiovisual Education, Division of, 1970s-1990s
  - Auxiliary Services, 1970s-2000s
  - Blank cards, 1980s, 1990s
  - John Burness family, 1990s
  - Cultural Services, 1980s, 1990s
  - Library, 1990s
  - Miscellaneous individuals, 1940-2000s
  - Miscellaneous University departments, 1980s, 1990s
  - Office of the University Secretary, 1990s
  - Notes, undated
  - Presidents Office, 1960s-
  - Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1990s
  - Washington Duke Inn and Golf Club, 1990s